Devin 我在后门这边 我要进去了
Devin, I'm at the back entrance. I'm going in.
没关系 是我
Okay, it's me.
爸爸?
Daddy?
你很安全 你很安全
You're okay. Yeah, you're okay.
好了 我们现在一起离开这地方
Okay, we're gonna get out of this place now.
走吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
拉住我的手
Hold my hand. Hold my hand.
嘿 Drummer 能听见吗
Yo, Drummer, you copy?
Dev 请回答
Dev, made contact...
小心 小心 后退
Back, back, back, back.
好了 没事了 接着走
All right, you're okay. Come on.
爸爸!
Daddy!
走 走
Come on, come on.
我们出来了
We got away.
好吧 我们还得回去
All right, we're going back in!
我们的机遇之地
Land of opportunity
正是将其提供给了我们的敌人
is offering just that to our enemies.
其产生的巨大破坏 正是国防部长
The magnitude of destruction our director of defense,
联合国
the United Nations,
以及疾控中心都警告过我们的...
and the Centers for Disease Control warning us about?
片名：战士的承诺  |  翻译by @Ash十架
我不知道如何向你形容
I don't know the words to tell you
我有多希望此刻与你在一起...
how I wish I could be where you are...
保护你...
protect you...
抱住你
hold you.
如果有办法 能让我把你从这场战争中救出
If there was a way, I would save you from this war...
它毁掉了一切...
which has covered everything...
你 你妈妈
you, your mom...
还有我们这个世界
our world...
每天早晨 我都看见你的脸
Every morning, I see your face.
听见你的笑声
I hear your laugh...
和你的小脚丫 踩在客厅地板上的声响
your footsteps on the living room floor.
每天夜里 我都梦见你出生的那一刻
Every night I dream when you were bom.
现在我满脑子想的 都是你是否安全
Now I wonder if you're safe.
你是否会为我担心 就像我为你和你妈妈担心一样
You can fear for me as much as I fear for you and your mom.
我不会停止寻找的 Johnny
I won't stop looking, Johnny.
我不会放弃的
I won't quit.
在海军陆战队 他们教会我
They taught us that in the Corps.
永远不要放弃
Never give up.
永远不要
Ever.
进来
Come in.
上尉 您找我吗
Captain, missing debrief?
你是Drummer下士吧
Corporal Drummer.
是准下士 长官
Lance Corporal, sir.
我是Peyton上尉 很荣幸终于与你见面
Ah. Captain Peyton. Nice to finally meet you.
我也很荣幸见到您 很抱歉我迟到了 睡过头了
It's a pleasure to meet you. I'm sorry I'm late. I overslept.
这几周实在难熬 坐吧 这就是我的城堡啦
It's been a tough couple of weeks. Please, my chateau.
有什么需要的吗
Can I get you anything?
来杯水就好 一杯可乐吧
Just a water, a Coke.
好的 我们为了审案 特意准备了个小冰箱
Well, we have a mini fridge for the court case.
啊 那蛮好的
That's a nice perk.
正好有几瓶 给你
We get a few over here.
含蔗糖的
It's got cane sugar.
墨西哥人做的就是好喝
Mexicans do it right, don't they?
那是你儿子吗?
That your son?
是教子 叫Zachary
Godson. Zachary.
你只有教子吗 还是也有自己的孩子?
You got kids of your own, or just the godson'?
好了 现在我们是来谈你的事
Well, right now, I'm here with you.
是这样 这个会议 比在那件事故发生后你经历的
So, this will be more informal than other meetings
其他会议都要随便一些
you may have had over the incident,
但如果你愿意的话
but if you would,
我想听你给我说一说你自己
I'd like you to tell me a little bit about yourself...
你在陆战队之外的生活
your life outside the Corps.
没什么的
It's not much.
我也不知道 你那文件里大概都写了 是不
I don't know, you probably got it all in there, don't you?
写了一些吧 我更想听你亲口说
Some of it. I'd prefer to hear it from you.
结婚八年
Married eight years.
育有一子
One child.
对的 我儿子Jon
Yep. Jon.
Jonathan
Jonathan.
Jonathan Michael Drummer
Jonathan Michael Drummer.
那Roberts下士呢
What about Corporal Roberts?
你怎么描述你们俩的关系?
How would you describe your relationship with him?
他是我认识的最厉害的陆战队员
Most squared-away Marine I know. Um...
我爱他就像爱我的家人
Love him like family.
除了家人和他之外 我不信任任何人
Trust nobody in the work! With family but him.
只要扣下扳机 你就一辈子后悔
Pull one trigger, regret the rest of your life.
哈 去你妈的
Yeah, fuck it.
- 你不这么想吗? - 怎么想?
- You don't think like that? - Like what?
后悔啊 从没见你后悔过
Regrets. You ain't got no regrets.
哈?
Huh?
我说我从没见你后悔过
You ain't got no regrets.
我当然有后悔过
I have regrets.
说一个
Name one.
呃...
Well...
我后悔把你拉进这烂事儿里
I regret bringing you into this bullshit.
一路上他一直支撑 照顾着我
He carried me every step of the way.
我是说 如果不是Roberts 我可能早就死了
I mean, I probably wouldn't be here if it wasn't for Roberts.
那你现在对此怎么想?
And how does that make you feel now?
我不知道
Not sure.
呐 你总会有些想法的吧
Well, you must have some feelings about it.
想怎么...
About how...
我真的不知道
I mean, I don'! know.
我只是想回到儿子身边
I'm just trying to get back to my son.
那是肯定的 你一定很想念他
Of course you do. You miss him.
我不知道这会开得有啥必要
I don't see... what the point of all this is.
因为这是强制的规定
Well, because this is mandatory,
直到我的表时针指向七点
until my local clock strikes seven,
之间这段时间 你都得留在这儿 所以...
you're expected to remain, so...
我们可以把这段时间好好利用起来
we might as well make the most of it.
反正权在你手里 长官
You got all the power, sir.
如果你不愿意的话 那我们就不谈你儿子
But if you'd prefer, we need not talk about your son.
好 我不愿意
I'd like that.
你们这群傻逼都觉得 自己是陆战队大兵吗?
You motherfuckers think y'all Marines?
是的 长官!
Yes, Sergeant!
我问 你们这群傻逼都觉得 自己是陆战队大兵吗?
I said do you motherfuckers think y'all are Marines?
是的 长官!
Yes, Sergeant!
好大兵 为陆战队流血
Good Marines have bled for the Corps.
好大兵 为陆战队牺牲
Good Marines have died for the Corps.
你们是不是也认为自己 有这份荣耀为国捐躯?
Do you believe you deserve to die with that same honor?
是的 长官!
Yes, Sergeant!
我问 你们是不是也认为自己 有这份荣耀为国捐躯?
I said do you think you deserve to die with that honor?
是的 长官!
Yes, Sergeant!
行吧 你看看你们吓得!
Yeah. Y'all look scared!
你们可能是高高兴兴来参军
You might be happy to be a Marine,
但看看你们吓成什么样!
but you look scared!
正因如此 我才在你们生命中出现
And for that reason I am inserted into your life.
你们手里拿的纸
The papers you're holding
是你们新的来复枪的序列号
are the serial numbers to your new rifles.
你们把这数 以及
You will memorize these numbers
上面一堆其他乱七八糟信息 给我记住了
along with a whole slew of other information
必须记住!
I deem necessary!
- 明白没? - 明白 长官!
- Is that clear? - Yes, Sergeant!
你知道你现在拿的是张纸吗 大兵?
You understand you're holding a piece of paper, Marine?
知道 长官!
Yes, Sergeant!
一片纸有多重?
How much does a piece of paper weigh?
- 轻于鸿毛 长官! - 有多重?
- Nothing, Sergeant! - How much?
- 轻于鸿毛 长官! - 那你的胳膊为啥都给压弯了?
- Nothing, Sergeant! - Then why are your arms falling?
你的胳膊为啥都给压弯了? 为啥?
Why are your arms falling? Why are your arms falling'!
你的胳膊为啥都给压弯了? 告诉我为啥!
Why are your arms falling? Tell me why!
告诉我!
Tell me why! Tell me why!
我不知道 长官
I don't know, Sergeant.
你不知道为啥你胳膊弯了?
You don't know why your arms are falling'?
- 不知道 长官 - 抬起来!
- No, Sergeant. - Keep them up!
把这张纸给我好好举着!
Keep the piece of fucking paper!
做好准备 你们会被逼到新的高度
Be prepared to be pushed to new levels.
会被激怒 会被侮辱
Be prepared to be pissed off and on
直到你们像个陆战队员
until you become worthy of appearing
when the enemy says...
抬起来!
Again, keep them up!
捡起来!
Pick it up!
欢迎来到痛苦之地 大兵们!
Welcome to the pain, marines!
欢迎来到痛苦之地!
Welcome to the pain!
- 欢迎来到痛苦之地! - 欢迎来到痛苦之地!
- Welcome to the pain! - Welcome to the pain!
欢迎来哪儿? - 欢迎来到痛苦之地!
Welcome to the what? - Welcome to the pain!
分好组 开始跑步!
Buddy up and move onto the course.
- 是 长官 - 动起来!
- Yes, Sergeant. - Move! Move!
动起来! 走吧!
Move! Let's go!
别记那个傻逼的仇 我们能应付的
Forget that fool. We got this.
♪ Tum it around ♪
♪ You found that they were all wrong ♪
♪ All you had heard ♪
♪ Were ghosts of the words in a song ♪
快点! 快点!
Move it! Move it!
快点 哥们 快!
Let's go, bro! Let's go. Hurry up!
第二小组 他妈的给我快点!
Group two, hurry the fuck up!
他妈的快点啊兄弟!
Hurry the fuck up, brother!
快点啊!
Hurry the fuck up!
- 侧翼! 出发! - 出发!
- Flank! Set! - Move out!
封锁前线!
Close our front!
- 出发! - 我起来了 他看见我的话 我就死定了
- Move out! - I'm up, he sees me, I'm down!
- 卧倒! - 快!
- Stay down! - Move it!
闭上嘴!
Shut it off!
大兵 你他妈说啥呢?
What the fuck are you saying, Marine?
没有 长官!
Nothing, Sergeant!
我跟你说话了吗 大兵?
Was I talking to you, Marine?
没有 长官!
No, Sergeant, sir!
那你他妈为啥回答?
Then why the fuck are you answering for him?
- 我不知道 长官! - 你俩是基佬情侣吗?
- I don't know, Sergeant. - You two butt buddies, Marine?
- 不是 长官! - 他妈的起来!
- No, Sergeant. - Get the fuck up!
是 长官
Yes, Sergeant.
你这个大兵 满嘴是大粪
You got a mouthful of shit, Marine.
是沙子 长官
Sand, Sergeant.
滚吧
We need to go.
- 从头开始! - 是 长官!
- Back to the top! - Yes, Sergeant.
再来 再来!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
我本来是报名参加绿色和平组织的 （保护动物不遭捕猎等的组织）
I signed up for Greenpeace.
结果怎么被发配到这儿了?
How the fuck did we wind up here?
他妈的 每天都有海豚被杀啊 哥们
Fucking dolphins dying, dude.
我们本来能救海豚于水火的
We could be saving the dolphins, man.
刚才在那边 你应该告诉他这些
You should tell him that when we're out there.
是
That's right.
"Miller中士 我报的是绿色和平组织"
"Sergeant Miller, I signed up for Greenpeace, sir."
就这样
Stay.
说真的 你的脑袋比Johnny的还难剃
Seriously, you're worse than Johnny.
别动了 小心给你割个口子
Stop moving or I will cut you.
- Nat! - "老子削你哦"
- I'm not. - "I'm-a cut you."
- 怎样 酷不? - 哈哈 很酷
- That was good, right? - That was pretty good.
好 我不动了 你剃吧
All right, come on. I'll stop fucking around. Go.
啊!
Ow!
嗷!
行了 别嚎了 你真是个胆小鬼
Okay, stop. God, you're such a wimp.
♪ I reached out to undress you ♪
♪ Love let me down ♪
- 你还好吗? - 很好
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 真的没事吗? - 没什么 就是睡不着觉
- Hey, are you okay? - Yeah, I just can't sleep.
我是说 就是睡一会儿就醒 懂吗?
I mean, I sleep but then I'm up, you know?
一直睡睡醒醒的
Just back and forth.
今天我去送孩子吧
I'll take him today.
也该你送了
You should take him today.
跟老师好好谈谈
Talk to the teacher.
学校里的小孩欺负他
Kids giving him problems.
对 跟老师谈一谈
Yeah, you need to talk to the teacher,
还有 有个家长 孩子妈
and then talk to that one mom.
- 哪个? 哪个家长? - 就那个女的 可讨厌了
- Which one? Which one? - I hate that woman.
那个胖小子他妈
The fat kid's mom. She...
那天我差点揍她了
I almost punched her the other day.
我是说 在想象中 我真揍她了
I mean, in my mind I punched her.
- 你真是个恶棍 - 嗯 没错
- You're a thug. - Yeah, that's right.
你老婆是个混黑道的
Your wife's a thug.
- 我是认真的 - 我爱你
- I'm serious. Come on. - I love you.
是吗? 看着我的脸说
Yeah? Say it to my face.
我爱你
I love you.
你最好爱我
You better.
你看起来不错 像个大兵了
You look good. You look like a Marine.
好的
Good.
走吧 你该去送孩子了
Get out. You gotta take him.
好
Yeah.
过来 我也给你剃一下...
Let me just get it right here.
别忘了跟那个家长说啊!
Tell that mom!
我看见你了
I see you.
你在那儿才看不见我
You can't see me from there.
我能啊 我现在就看着你呢
Yeah, I can. I'm looking right at you.
你瞎说什么 我这就能看见你
What are you talking about? I see you right there.
还能看见
Nope, still see you.
现在看不见了
Now I can't see you,
但是如果我看不见你的话 你也就看不见我了
but if I can't see you, you can't see me.
为什么?
Why is that?
我也不知道 就是这个规律
I don't know why is that, it's just the rules.
你在学校学啥了?
What are you learning in school?
学到了什么有意思的东西吗?
You learning fun stuff?
就读书啊 然后课间休息
We read, do recess,
听音乐 跳舞
listen to music, dance.
休...什么玩意...跳舞?
Rec... What kind of...? Dancin' around?
这怎么听着这么作啊 哥们
That sounds very arty-fatty to me, bud.
说到这儿...
Speak of the devil...
- 爸爸! - 噢 不!
- Dad! - Oh, no!
是什么!
What is that!
你最好把窗户打开 兄弟
You'd better get the window, bud.
- 我要死了! - 不!
- I'm gonna die! - Oh, no!
噢 不! 全体都有 撤离! 医务兵 有友军倒下!
Oh, no! Marines, clear out! Medic, man down!
呃...
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
他还有反应吗? 还有反应吗?
Is he responding? Is he responding?
- 啊 还有反应 - 好了 好了!
- He's responding. - Okay, okay, okay, okay!
- 你说的那是什么意思? - "反应"吗?
- What does that mean? Responding?
不是, "友军倒下"
No, "man down."
"友军倒下"是个军事术语 意思是
Man down is a military term. It's what you say when...
我方的兄弟被击倒 或者受伤了 这样
one of your boys goes down or someone gets hurt, or...
哦
Oh.
让我猜猜是哪个孩子欺负人
Let me take a wild guess of who that is.
是那个小子吗?
Is that him right there?
我跟你一起过去 这样他就不敢欺负你了
I'm gonna come in with you so they don't mess with you.
- 不要! 求你了 - 为什么
- No! Please. Why?
- 就是... - 咋了 你觉得跟我一起很尴尬吗
- It's just... - What are you embarrassed of me?
我一个人可以走过去的 真的
I can walk from here, really.
我知道你可以 你是个大孩子了
I know you can walk from here. You're a grown boy.
这是怎么开始的? 某天他们无缘无故就开始欺负你?
How'd this start up? You just walked in one day and they started in on you?
- 不是 - 那是怎么回事?
- No. - What happened?
有次他们听见妈妈送我的时候 说了句"我爱你"
They heard Mom say "I love you" when she dropped me off.
她在你朋友面前说了 "我爱你"?
She said "I love you" in front of your friends, huh?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
好吧 我明白了 这样不好
All right, I understand. It's no good.
- 你给妈妈讲过吗? - 嗯
- And you told Mom? - Yeah.
她说什么?
What'd she say?
他说他要把那些孩子的家长们揍一顿
She said she was gonna beat the mother up.
她说要把那些家长揍一顿? 好吧 听着
She was gonna beat the mothers up? All right, look.
我不是妈妈 但是我肯定
I'm not mom, but I damn sure am gonna tell my kid
我也想在你下车时跟你说"我爱你"
I love him when he gets out the car, all right?
所以我们想个能过得去的办法吧
So we gotta come up some kind of little middle ground,
比如一个暗号什么的
like a secret word or something.
"友军倒下"好不好?
What about "man down"?
- "友军倒下"? - 很好吧
- Man down? - That's pretty good.
- 怎么样? - 嗯 我喜欢 "友军倒下"
- Huh? Yeah. - Yeah, I like that. Man down.
我也喜欢
I like it, too.
里面有"军"字 听起来多男人啊
It's got the word "man" in it, damn sure is manly enough.
这个暗号 我们想什么时候说都可以
You know, we'll just sneak it out anytime we want to say it.
没其他人会知道这是什么意思
Nobody will know what we're talking about.
所以 如果我想说"我爱你"的话 我会怎么说?
So, anytime I want to say I love you what am I going to say to you?
- "友军倒下" - 对 就这样
- Man down. - Like that, too,
再带上你脸上那小笑容
with that little smirk on your face.
- 再说一遍 - "友军倒下"
- Say it again. - Man down.
好了 小子 没事了 走吧
Yes, good, man. All right, get out of here.
祝你一天过得愉快
Have a good day, bud.
你也是
You too.
Drummer 嘿Drummer 收到吗?
Drummer. Yo, Drummer, you copy?
我在这边发现一个怪人
I got a tudy up ahead
大约在主院东南方向一百码
approximately 100 yards southeast of the main courtyard.
就那儿
Right there.
他妈怎么回事?
What the fuck?
这人在这儿坐了多久了? 你呢?
How long's he been sitting there? And yourself?
我也不知道 我们走吧
I'm not sure. Come on, let's go.
怎么回事?
What the fuck?
别动!起来 起来!
Don't move. Get up. Up. Move.
滚到那个墙角去
Down in that corner.
坐下 你是谁?
Down. Who are you?
我们是美国海军陆战队员 你要是敢轻举妄动 我一枪崩了你的头
United States Marines. If you try anything, I take your head off!
- 明白没? - 你是谁?
- Got that clean'? - Who are you?
回答问题
Answer the question.
你是谁?
Who are you?
Charles 我叫Charles
Charles. My name is Charles.
Charles? 嘿 Charles 喘口气 喘口气
Charles? Hey, Charles. Take a breath. Breathe.
我叫Gabriel
My name's Gabriel.
我在寻找幸存者 明白?
I'm looking for survivors, you understand?
好
Okay, man.
你知道这里发生了什么吗?
What do you know about what happened here?
什么发生...?
What happened to...?
什么? 世界怎么变成这样? 你怎么没被感染?
To who? The world. How come you weren't affected?
你怎么没被感染?
How come you weren't affected?
我靠
Oh, please.
这世界都变成一坨屎 为什么你没被感染?
How is it the whole world is in shit and you're not affected?
这是夸我呢? 可惜我不需要你的夸奖
Save your compliments for someone who'd want to hear them.
- 这世界完蛋了 - 你独自一人吗?
- This whole world's fucked. - You're alone?
有跟你一起的幸存者吗?
You got survivors with you?
我朋友 还有我的整个排
I got my friends. I got my whole platoon.
在哪儿? 他们在哪儿?
Where? Where are thew
- 嘿! 在那儿别动 - 别动
- Hey! Stay right there. - Don't move.
这什么?
What is it?
你也是海军?
You semper fi?
很久很久以前了 兄弟
That was a long time ago, buddy.
遥远得像是另一个世界 不过现在都没关系了
Whole 'nother world, but it don't matter none.
他们把我们留在地狱里腐烂
They all left us here in hell to rot.
谁?
Who did?
你
You did.
是你
You.
是这样 多年来 我一直在观察 或者说是发表
Look, I've been analyzing or pontificating
关于这个议题的变化的论证
on variations of this theme for years.
今天 我只说事实
Today I'll state only facts.
在中东 正在进行一场小型战争
There's a mini war in the Middle East.
伊朗最有可能拥有核武器
Iran will most likely have a nuclear weapon.
普京基本上是个失控的疯子
Putin basically running unchecked,
很显然是一个需要关注的大问题
obviously a great cause for concern.
哥们儿 这些小家伙快从盒子里跳出来了
Dude, this little guys gonna jump out of the fucking box.
放下吧
Well, put her down.
再等等吧 小东西
Not yet, little buddy.
你看这个没?
Did you see this?
我卡车里还有一堆水球
I've got some bowls for water in the truck.
呃 礼物不错
No. Nice present.
疾病控制中心
Centers for Disease Control...
他很喜欢的
- He loves it. - Has downgraded the urgency.
现在"大规模杀伤性武器"这个术语
While the term "weapons of mass destruction"
已经变成一个政治禁忌
has become a political taboo,
没人可以否认 疾控中心
no one can deny that the CDC, the Centers for Disease Control,
将会比以往更频繁地成为主角
has been the lead story more frequently than ever.
好 我这就去把小寿星叫进来 行吧?
Okay, I'm bringing the birthday boy in, all right?
好的
Yeah. Yeah.
11点有重播的 是吧?
That comes on again at 11, right?
- 好啦 - 走吧 小伙伴
- All right! - Come on, pal!
嘿!
Hey!
好啦 现在你告诉我 这个世界上你最想要的东西是什么?
Now, what did you want more than anything in the world, bud?
够吃一整年的小熊糖!
A year's supply of gummy bears!
比小熊糖更好的
- More than gummy bears! - All right, listen, your dad...
这什么声音?
What's that noise?
- 是小熊糖吗? - 不是
- That sound like gummy bears? - No.
这是什么声音呀?
What's that noise, bud?
你爸爸和我一直在说的...
Your daddy and I talked about all the...
这听着像什么? 像什么? 一只小狗狗!
What's that sound like? What's that sound like? A puppy!
我的天呀! 狗狗! 超可爱!
Oh. my gosh! A puppy! So cute!
- 别抱太紧了 - 天呀 谢谢
- Don't squeeze him too hard. - Oh, my gosh, thank you.
你喜欢吗?
What do you think?
- 他好棒! - 他喜欢哦
- He's amazing! - Oh, he loves him.
要给Luke看看吗? 去给Luke看看狗狗吧
Wanna show Luke? Go show Luke the dog.
- 小心点 - 去给Luke看看狗
- Be careful. - Go show Luke the dog.
大家快来看!狗狗!
Everyone, look! It's a puppy!
- 他好喜欢哦 - 是啊
- He loves it. - Yeah.
谢谢
- Thank you. - Yeah.
没有你我做不到的
I wouldn't have done that without you.
嗯 小心点!
Yeah. Be careful!
- 别告诉我我错过了那一幕 - 你错过了
- Don't tell me I missed that. - You missed that.
是吗? 他欣喜若狂了?
What? He lose his shit?
狂得不行了 我去跟他玩一会儿
Lost it. I'm gonna party with him.
看看他
There he is.
你要向我射击吗?
Okay. You gonna shoot me?
你要给他起什么名字?
What are you gonna name the dog?
我想叫他伊卡伯
I was thinking Ichabod.
你知道"狗狗帽"吗?
What do you know about dog hats? What do you know about dog hats'?
你想要狗狗帽吗?
You want dog hats?
你没戴过狗狗帽吗? - 没有!
You've never had a dog hat? - Nope!
嘿 Luke 你呢 你知道狗狗帽吗?
Hey, Luke, what do you know about dog hats?
他会没事的
He'll be all right.
- 过来 Luke - 真好玩!
把眼睛闭上
Close your eyes.
等我喷了药就别再揉眼睛
Do not rub your eyes once I apply the application.
- 收到 长官 - 深呼吸
- Roger, Sergeant. - Take a deep breath.
准备好了就转过身来
Turn around when you're ready. OC, OC.
睁眼 这是几?
Open your eyes. How many fingers am I holding up?
- 睁眼 - 二 长官
- Open them. - Two, Sergeant.
- 走吧! - 好了 快走 快点!
- Move, go! - That's right, let's go! Let's go!
动作快点!
Let's go, move!
给我用力 大兵!
Get bad, Marine, get bad!
Get back, get back, get back, get back!
进攻了! 散开!
This is our push! Spread out!
动作快点! 动起来!
Move! Move! Let's go!
加速! 加速!
Speed up! Speed up!
继续! 继续前进!
Let's go! Let's go! Keep moving! Keep moving!
Get back, get back, get back, get back, get back, get back!
走! 快走!
Just go! Let's go!
大兵 你这是干什么?
What the fuck are you doing, Marine?
你他妈干嘛揉眼睛?
Why the fuck are you rubbing your eyes?
- 我什么都看不见 长官 - 你当然看不见
- I can't see, Sarge. - Of course you can't see.
你眼睛闭着呢
Your fucking eyes are closed.
所以你觉得解决这个问题的 最简单的方法是什么?
What do you believe the simple solution to that would be'?
睁开眼 长官
Open my eyes, Sarge.
这不就得了 自己想出了办法
Well, there you go! Figure this shit out.
看看这有多简单!
And look how fucking easy that was!
抬头挺胸 眼睛看着目标!
Keep your head up and eyes on the fucking target!
快看啊 哥们
Look at this shit, man.
真他妈美!
Huh? Fucking beautiful!
你们问 为什么要承受痛苦? 为什么要剥夺你们的权利?
You ask, why the pain? Why the deprivation?
去他妈的
Ah, fuck, man.
行吧 得了
All right, come on.
当你的敌人听到声音向你开火时
Pain doesn't subside as your enemy listens
痛苦不会平息
for sounds to fire towards.
快点 傻逼们 快点!
Move, motherfucker, move!
继续前进!
Keep moving! Keep moving!
把枪交了
Hand over your rifle.
Roberts 快帮帮你的哥们
Roberts, help out your fellow Marine.
给他拿水冲冲眼睛
Looks like he could use some water.
下一个!
Next!
睁开眼 睁开眼
Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
加油 哥们 加油
Come on, brother, push it out. Come on.
加油
Push it out.
好吧 总得有人给最后一名鼓鼓掌咯
Well, somebody gotta applaud the Jamaican bobsled team.
我说的对吗 大兵们?
Am I right, Marines?
对 长官!
Yes, Sergeant!
- 我说的对吗? - 对 长官!
- Am I right, Marines? - Yes, sir!
妈的
The fuck.
烧得我疼死了
That burns like a motherfucker.
疼死了
Like a motherfucker.
真他妈疼死了 哥们
Like a motherfucker, man.
快在那儿吹吧
Hit that fan. All right.
你会没事的 哥们 我爱你
You'll be all right, brother. Love you, man.
嘿 Miller中士 来讲几句怎么样?
Yo, Sergeant Miller, how about a speech?
来吧
Come on.
我讲了又没人给我钱 小屌贝
They don't pay me for speeches, little spoon.
- 他屌可大了 - 我听说的可不是这样
- It's big spoon, man. - Ain't what I heard.
我可是看过的哦
Peek at you, snuggling.
是的 长官
Sir.
好吧 再过短短几天
All right. Um, in a few short days,
你们就要被分配到各个部队
you guys will be assigned units,
执行自己的任务
and there you'll go where duty calls.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
所以也没什么好说的
So with not much left to say,
我只引用一句
I will leave you with the words
埃琳诺·罗斯福的名言
of the late, great, Eleanor Roosevelt,
说的是
who so eloquently stated,
"在这个世界上 我见过的海军陆战队员
"The Marines I've seen around this world
拥有最洁净的身体
have the cleanest bodies,
最肮脏的心灵 最高的士气
filthiest minds, highest morale...
以及在我所见过的任何动物群体之中
and lowest morals
最低的道德标准"
of any group of animals I've ever seen."
你为什么盯着我看?
Why are you looking at me, man?
感谢上帝让我们拥有美国海军陆战队!
Thank God for the United States Marine Corps!
- 喔喔喔! 耶! - 喊起来!
- Hooah! Yeah! - Let's give him one!
吃饭吧 我要吃了
Eat up. I'm-a eat.
- 你要什么? - 给我个热狗 大屌贝
- What you want? - Give me a hotdog, big spoon.
好
All right.
给我也拿一个
Hey, bring me one.
说得很好
Great speech.
嗯
Yeah.
没有什么能比埃琳诺·罗斯福这话
Nothing like an Eleanor Roosevelt quote
更能鼓舞士气了
to get the crowd going.
- "埃莉诺" - 是埃琳诺 宝贝
- "Elyeanor." - It's Eleanor, baby.
我是学他呢
I'm just saying it 'cause he said it.
投得好 Jon!
Good throw, Jon!
上旋球漂亮 宝贝!
Nice spiral, baby!
- 你这孩子真会扔! - 是啊
- Kid's got an arm, man! - Yeah, he does.
送孩子去小足队吧 我说
Peewee league, man, that's all I'm saying.
这主意还真不错
That's a good idea, actually.
- 小足队 - 你觉得呢?
- Peewee league. Yeah. - You think?
可能对他也有好处
I guess it would be good for him
在你不在的时候 他可以跟其他孩子的爸爸一起相处
to be around other dads and stuff while you're away.
- 可以啊 - 好吧
- Yeah. - Yeah.
好啊
So, yeah.
嗯 如果能让她开心的话
Yeah, if it makes him happy, yeah.
肯定会让他开心的 嘿 Jon!
It'll make him happy. Jon! Hey, Jon!
你想去小足队打球吗?
What do you think about peewee league?
想!
Yeah!
- 小足队? - 想
- Peewee league? - Yeah.
- 说定了 - 说定了
- Sold. - Sold.
给我扔一球 Jon
Throw me one, Jon.
- Devin Roberts下士 - 嗯哼
- Corporal Devin Roberts. - Mm-hmm.
我想了解一下你俩之间的关系
I'd like to understand the relationship between you both.
没什么可了解的 我俩在一个街区长大
There's not much to understand. We grew up on the same block.
他父母把他赶出家门 我父母收留了他
His parents kicked him out, my parents took him in,
然后那段时间我们两个人 碰巧有了共同的目标 就一起走了
and right around the time we ran into things in common, we shipped off.
去打仗了
To war.
嗯 去打仗了
他是我的战友
He's my battle buddy.
我们一起踢开敌人的大门 承受敌人的进攻...
We kicked in doors together, we took enemy fire...
这种关系 如果不亲身经历的话...
it's just not a relationship you'd understand...
我猜你是不会懂得的
if you haven't been through it, I guess.
这样 我听过很多人讲述这样的故事
Well, I've seen it discussed a lot,
不如你给我讲讲?
so why don't you try me?
"很多人讲过"?
"Discussed a lot."
怎么了 很可笑吗?
Something funny about that?
那不一样的
It's just different.
"地面部队"
Boots on the ground.
是吗?
Yeah?
我不是说这个
Yeah, it's not that,
只是这种事讲不出的
it's just something you don't discuss.
你看见了什么
What you saw.
我叫Gabriel Drummer 在找我的家人
My name's Gabriel Drummer. I'm looking for my family.
我靠 好棒呢
Oh, well, fucking A.
看着我 我会给你看样东西
Look at me. I'm going to show you, okay?
你看看这张照片
I need you to look at the photo.
Charles 你看这张照片
Show you this photo, Charles.
这是我的老婆孩子
This is my wife and son.
你是跟那个大天使加百列同名吗
Gabriel the archangel.
你能不能看一眼这照片?
Can you look at the photo?
我啥都不知道
I don't know anything, man.
- 看看这张照片 Charles - 我什么都不知道
- Look at the photo, Charles. - I don't know anything.
看照片! 你认出他们了吗?
Look at it! Do you recognize the faces?
- 这儿一个人都没有 - 你见过他们吗?
- Ain't nobody here, man. - Have you seen these people?
- 这儿一个人都没有 - 这不是有你吗
- Ain't nobody here, man. - Yeah, but you.
你不是在这儿吗
But you. You're here.
现在你也在了
And now you.
嘿 你觉得我不敢杀你吗?
Hey, you think I won't kill you?
你觉得我不敢杀你吗 Charles?
You think I won't kill you, Charles?
- 不敢 - 不敢?
- No. - No?
我是说 你敢...
I mean, yeah...
你觉得我不敢杀了你?
You think I won't kill you? Hmm?
- 不敢 - 看着我
- No. - Look at me.
我是说 敢 我敢...
Yes. I mean, yes, I will.
让这傻逼去死吧 咱们拿着他的东西走吧
Yo, fuck this fool, man. Let's just take his shit and go.
你需要睡一觉 Charles 这附近有庇护所吗?
You need sleep, Charles. You got shelter around here?
- Charles - 回答问题
- Charles. - Answer the question.
你家在哪儿?
Where's home?
那边
Over there.
拿上你的东西 Charles
Get your shit, Charles.
嘿 小子 你吃完了没?
Hey, you almost done, little man?
我要出去了
I'm gonna go outside.
我跟Johnny学校的老师
Hey, so I was talking to some of the aides
谈了一些学校橄榄球队的事
over at Johnny's school about the little football program.
你是说小足队?
Peewee league?
嗯 他们说会安排一些晚上的活动
Yeah, they said they're gonna have it at night
这样我上夜班就轻松些
with some other activities when I'm at work.
那很好
That's perfect.
他们为你准备了一个爱心包裹
They're already putting together all these care packages for you,
很贴心的
all kinds of sweet things.
我无所谓的 你知道
I'm easy, you know.
随便什么我都没问题
Just peanut butter anything, and I'm good.
Jon?
Right, Jon?
- 你还好吧? - 嗯
- You all right, pal? - Yeah.
Gabe
Gabe. - Hey.
Gabe 我能不能跟你单独待一会儿?
Gabe, can I please just have a minute with you?
好
Yeah.
所以这是干嘛 你要假装
What, so you're just going to pretend
一切都没发生 你不会走吗?
like this isn't happening?
我不知道你想听我说什么 Nat
I mean, I don't know what you want me to say, Nat.
- 我受不了当个单亲妈妈 Gabe - 你不是单亲妈妈
- I can't be a single mom, Gabe. - You're not a single mom.
你知道 战争是真的 不是我编的
You know, there's a war going on, I'm not making it up.
我们报名时就知道的
It's something we were both aware of when we signed up.
- 是你报名 不是我们 - 好吧 Natty
- When you signed up. - Okay, Natty.
还有 Devin要怎么办?
And what. What does Devin get to do'?
为什么他就能留在这里 因为胳膊断了吗?
Why does he get to stay back, 'cause he broke his arm?
他留在这儿有什么用?
I mean, he gets to stay back for what?
因为我们也需要有人留守啊
Because we need a presence here as well.
为什么? 有谁打进美国了吗?
Why? Who the fuck's attacking America?
你会没事的 Nat
You're gonna be okay, Nat.
真的吗?
Really?
Gabe 那可是阿富汗
Afghanistan, Gabe?
你以为我是愿意去
You think that I want to do this,
特别想去
that this is something I want to do,
好像我等不及去打仗一样?
like I can't wait to go to war?
你知道吗 我想留在这儿 跟你在一起 Natty
You know, I'd love to stay here and just be here with you, Natty,
但是我不能 我别无选择
but I can't do that. That's not an option for me.
天啊...
Man...
对不起
I'm sorry.
这对于我来说也很难
You know, it's not easy for me, either.
你也生我气 他也生我气...
You're mad and he's mad and...
我没生气 我是伤心! 他也伤心!
No, I'm sad, and he's fucking sad,
整个邻里都伤心!
and the whole neighborhoods sad.
别这样 Nat 过来
Stop. Hey, come on. Stop, Nat.
Natty 对不起
Natty, I'm sorry.
别这样
Come on.
会没事的
We're gonna be fine.
我们会没事的
Hey, we're gonna be fine. Come on.
别看我
Don't look at me.
我们会没事的
We're gonna be fine.
- 我爱你 - 我爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
嘿 小伙子
Hey, bud.
- 你要走了 - 是的
- You're leaving. - Yeah.
你不想玩了? 为什么?
You won't play anymore? Why?
你知道吗 我在想...
You know, I was thinking about...
在想...
I was thinking about...
过去 我们都是寄信的
You know, in the old days, we used to send letters.
在很久很久以前
I mean, way back, you know.
那可是超级庞大的一个工程
It was, like, a big process.
信必须是手写的
You had to, like, write it by hand.
还要找张邮票 再找一个信箱
You had a find a stamp, find a mailbox.
总之是件相当大的事
It was just this whole big thing.
现在都没人这么做了
Now, we don't have to do that anymore,
因为有了电子邮件 视频聊天...
'cause now we got email and Skype...
就好像对方就在你身边 明白吗?
It's almost like I'm here already, you know?
我也是一样 不知不觉中 我就会回到你身边的
And before you know it, I will be.
明白吗?
You know?
我想送你个东西
I could give you something.
好啊
Yeah.
是什么?
What is it?
是我和妈妈
It's me and Mom.
哇!
Oh!
妈妈知道你有这张照片吗?
Mom know you have this?
你这狡猾的小鬼
You sneaky little weasel.
我爱你
I love you, man.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
那你到了那儿之后
And when you get there,
会给我写信吗?
will you do that letter thing with me?
会啊 我一到那儿就给你写
Yeah, I'll do the letter thing as soon as I get there.
等我一落地就开始写
Soon as I land, I'll start with the letter thing.
天天都写 行不?
In hand, every day. All right?
看着我 "友军倒下"
Look at me. Man down.
"友军倒下"
Man down.
好啦
All right.
最后一站啦
Last stop.
你知道吗 是你把我拉进来的
You know, it was you that got me into this shit.
是 但是当时看起来像个好主意
Yeah, well, seemed like a good idea at the time.
嗯
Mm.
嘿 你也可以把你的手伸到窗外去啊 (负伤就不用去了)
Hey, man, you could always put your arm through a fucking window.
是
Yeah.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this shit.
兄弟 你是我这辈子唯一的亲人
You're the only family I ever had, man.
得了 不要说这些矫情的
All right, don't do that shit now.
帮我照顾我的家人 好吗?
Just watch out for mine, all right?
- 你知道我会的 - 我知道你会
- You know I will. - L know you will.
好吧 别忘了给我发照片
All right, send me pictures and...
我知道你想看啥样的照片
I know what kind of pictures you want.
嗯 好的
Yeah, all right.
在那边别像个婊子似的!
Don't be a bitch out there!
你了解我的
You know me.
我不知道他在哪儿...
I don't know where he is...
我不知道Johnny在哪儿
I don't know where Johnny is.
你说什么?
What'd you say?
嘿 你刚说什么?
Hey, what did you just say?
- 你说什么? - 没啥 我不知道...
- What'd you say? - Nothing. I didn't...
你刚才说了"Johnny"
No, you just said "Johnny," man.
你认出照片里的男孩了?
You recognize the boy in the photo?
- 什么? - 我的儿子
- What? - My son?
- 我谁也没认出啊 - 胡扯
- I don't recognize anyone. - That's bullshit.
胡扯 他撒谎
That's bullshit, man. He's lying to you.
他刚才说了Johnny的名字
He just said Johnny's name.
我以性命发誓 他刚说了你儿子的名字
On my life, he just said your son's name, man.
他说了
He said it.
我们走吧
Let's just get where we're going.
- 喂? - Devin
- Hello? - Devin.
嘿!
Yo.
- 嘿 - 这他妈是谁啊
- Hey. - What the fuck...
不好意思 你那边很晚了吧
Hey, sorry I'm calling late, man.
你有事吗现在?
You doing something right now?
- 呃 没有 - 能聊聊天吗?
- Uh, n-no. - Can you talk?
能啊 哥们
Yeah, man.
我只是想跟Natalie说说话
I was trying to get ahold of Natalie,
但是我打电话和视频都找不到她 所以...
but I can't get her on cell or Skype. so...
哦 没关系 哥们 可以
Yeah, yeah, no, of course, man.
呃 我想她应该挺忙的吧最近
Um, yeah, I think, you know, I think she's been pretty hectic
Johnny要练球
with Johnny's, you know, practice,
她又要上夜班 还有别的事...
and working late and whatever, so...
如果你担心的话 我可以去你家看一眼啊
But I can go 'round and check it out if you're worried.
- 你可以吗? - 当然啦 哥们
- Yeah, can you do that? - Yeah, man, of course.
- Johnny怎么样? - Johnny很好的 哥们
- How's Johnny? - Johnny's great, man.
他很好 做得很棒
He's good, yeah. He's killing it.
- 真的吗! - 是啊 超级厉害的
- Really! - Man, he's murdering, bro.
Romo都没有他厉害
Roma's got nothing on that kid, man.
真的吗!
No!
当然 我也不是说Romo有多好
Not that Rome's got anything on anybody,
- 你知道的 - 我知道
- you know how it is. - Yeah.
那 你那边呢 很糟吗?
So, it's pretty fucked up over there, huh?
嗯 很糟
Yeah, it's pretty fucked up.
听着 好消息
Listen, good news.
我马上就要跟你会合去了 大概一周左右就到
Um, I'm headed your way, like, a week from tomorrow.
不可能
Get outta here.
- 是真的 - 哇
- Yeah, for real. - Wow.
我胳膊上的石膏卸了 哥们 马上就去找你了
Yeah, I got this thing off my arm, bro. I'm coming.
真好
That's great.
是啊
Yeah.
反正 你知道的
Anyway, you know,
我想谢谢你为了我跑一趟
I just want to thank you for going to check on things.
呃 得了 分内事
Oh, come on, man, of course.
- 嗯 - 没问题的
- Yeah. - Of course.
你要是见到Natty 帮我转告她 我爱她
If you see Natty, tell her I love her.
我会的
I will.
跟她说让她看看手机 接电话
Tell her to pick up her cell phone.
- 好的知道了 - 好
- Yeah, okay, man. - All right.
你的地址是 明尼苏达大街 2273号 对吗?
Your address, 2273 Minnesota Street, is that correct?
对 长官
Yes, sir.
你的妻子和儿子也在那里居住吗?
And that's where your wife and child reside?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我不知道你问我这些干什么 长官
I don't really see what that has to do with anything, sir.
你为什么一直看那些文件
Why you keep looking at that paper.
你不想让我看吗?
Would you rather I not?
我不知道
I don't know.
你问我地址干什么?
Is there a reason you asked about my address?
只是想确定你是你自己
Just making sure you're you.
好吧
Okay.
我是不是我自己?
Am I me?
是的
I believe so.
我们干嘛不聊聊坎德什?
Why don't we talk about Kamdesh?
我是说 我到这儿来不正是因为那事吗?
I mean, that's the reason I'm here, isn't it?
好吧
Okay.
坎德什
Kamdesh.
他们下次能不能把这破车
Can they give the shit vehicles
分配给陆军啊? 真他妈狗屎玩意
to the Army next time? This is bullshit.
- 机器总是会坏的 大兵 - 是的
- Machines break down, Marine. - Yes, they do.
我们这里一切正常 这片区域安全
We're all good up here. This area is secure.
大兵 我们这是在打仗 不存在什么安全区域
We're at war, Marine. Nothing's secure.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
发糖时间 不给糖就捣蛋
Candygram. Trick or treat.
他们还想我手把手送过去啊
They want a fucking hand delivery.
所以我才从来不给
Yeah, that's why I don't bother.
你胳膊咋样了 Roberts?
How's the arm, Roberts?
- 好的不得了 - 是吗?
- Great. - Yeah?
- 是 - 你关照得很好嘛?
- Yeah. Uh-huh. - You've been whacking it?
Drummer呢? 你也关照他了吗?
How about Drummer? You been whacking Drummer'?
- 嗯哼 - 下面怎样了 Jones?
- Yep. - How we doing down there, Jones?
还有两分钟就能启动了
Two minutes should be good to pull her out, sir.
大家都打起精神了!
Let's keep our heads on, Marines!
来嘛 是糖果啊! 大家都爱糖果
Come on, it's candy! Everybody likes it.
他们不喜欢 我真不知道这些孩子想要什么
They don't like the candy. I can't get anything out of these kids.
你看到二楼那人了吗?
You see him on the second deck?
他们想要无麸质的健康食品
They say gluten-free.
- 闭嘴吧 - 马上就好了 长官
- Shut the fuck up. - Just about good here, sir.
这些孩子是他妈的在节食减肥还是怎么着
These kids must be on the fucking Atkins Diet, or some shit.
马上就好了 长官!
Sir, we're just about good here!
长官 我看到二楼有动静 第七间
Sir, I got movement, second deck, 2-7.
好了 准备好!
All right, back her up! Ready to go!
妈的!
Oh, fuck!
突然爆炸! 突然爆炸!
I.E.D.! I.E.D.!
Yeah!
妈的!
What the fuck!
快去用上面那柄.50!
Pull that 50!
我们的战斗部队
We've got troops in combat! Troops in combat!
Go, go!
找掩体!
Take cover!
二楼上的那个房间! 快!
Pull the pin! Second deck! We're moving!
快来 长官!
Come on, sir!
操!
Fuck!
原路折返!
Backtrack!
你他妈干嘛? 你手里拿的 是个破来复枪! 妈的!
What the hell are you doing? It's a carbide rifle! Fuck!
- 长官! - 接着!
- Sir! - Take it!
继续! 继续前进!
Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
我们安全!
We're good!
我操 我们这是在干嘛?
What the fuck. What the fuck are we doing here?
踹门!
Set!
手雷!
Grenade!
走走走!
Go, go, go!
你为什么不愿意谈谈
Is there a reason you don't want to discuss
你在那房间里看到了什么?
what you saw in that room?
我看见了什么 长官?
What I saw in the room, sir?
或者说 经历了什么
Experienced.
Gabriel 你经历了一系列的创伤事件
Gabriel, you've been through a series of traumatic events.
我不知道
I don't know.
我们还是翻篇儿吧 我会没事的 长官
I prefer if we just move on. I'll be fine, sir.
我向你保证 这些东西 不是你说翻篇就这么容易翻过去的
I'd assure you, these are things you do not simply move on from.
那你说我该怎么做呢?
What do you suggest that I do, then?
我们在这里就是要帮你 解决这个问题
That's what we're here to sort out.
不过没关系 我们还有一次 规定的强制会议
Either way, we have a mandatory date again.
这些所谓救助资金 都是那个希望我这样的人没了的政府出的?
Funded by a government who'd like to see people like me gone.
没了 是什么意思?
Gone?
如果你看了我们国家军人中的 自杀率统计数据
Maybe if you looked at the spike in suicide rates
大概就会明白你要找的是什么了
of military personnel in this country, you'd know what you're looking for.
是什么呢?
And what would that be?
你的手是有什么毛病吗?
Has that been a problem?
- Gabriel - 是 长官
- Gabriel. - Yes, sir.
你提到了自杀
You brought up suicide.
为什么会提起自杀呢?
Is there a reason you did that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不想我的孩子受到伤害
I just don't want my kid to hurt.
当然
Of course.
你想杀了我 是吗?
You want to kill me, don't you?
我只是想找到我儿子
I just want to find my son.
你是海军陆战队的吗?
You're a Marine, huh?
呼哈
Hoorah.
你知道我儿子在哪儿吗 Charles?
You know where my son is, Charles?
我谁也没看到过
I haven't seen anybody.
我知道的话早告诉你了
I'd tell you if I did.
那他妈是什么?
What the fuck is that?
那是什么?
What is that?
那栋楼里有人
There's people in that building.
- 是谁? - 我不...不知道
- Who are they? - I don't... I don't know.
- 我没看... - 他们是美国人吗?
- I don't see... - Are they Americans?
我怎么会知道
Fuck if I know, man.
他们可能还会在边境铺条红毯
They might as well roll the red carpet out on these borders,
让世界各地的人进入 这个该死的国家
people they let into this goddamned country.
我操
Holy fuck.
你对自己朋友干嘛都完全不关心吗?
Still not concerned about what you friend here is up to, huh?
这儿他妈有个手机 兄弟
That's a motherfucking cell phone, dog.
Dev 那楼里有人
Dev, there's people in my building.
- 就在那边 - 什么?
- In that building. - What?
那边有人
There's people.
你刚才不是说没人吗
You just said there was nobody here.
- 那边楼里明明就有人 - 谁在那边?
- There's people in that building. - Who's over there?
那栋楼里有小孩吗?
They got kids in the building?
是小孩吗? 你看到什么了 Drummer?
There are kids over there? What you seeing, Drummer?
有小孩吗?
They got kids in that building?
你去哪儿? 嘿 我操!
Where you going? Hey, motherfucker!
- 你去哪儿啊 哥们? - 我哪儿也不去
- Where you going, man? - I'm not going anywhere.
- 你去哪儿? - 哪儿也不去
- Where you going? - I'm not going anywhere.
他想跑!
He's trying to run, man.
你用这个手机给谁打电话?
Who are you calling on this phone?
- 我没打... - 你用这个手机给谁打电话?
- I'm not calling... - Who are you calling on this phone?
什么?
What?
- 那是什么? - 你看到什么?
- What is this? - What do you see?
- 你看到什么了 Drummer? - 你怎么会有这个?
- What did you see, Drummer? - How did you get this?
这个信封你从哪里搞来的? 从哪里搞来的?
How did you get this envelope? How did you get this envelope?
- 听着 我不知道 - 这个信封你从哪里搞来的?
- Listen, I don't know. - How did you get this envelope?
这个信封上写的是我儿子的地址 这是我的信封 你怎么得到的?
It's an envelope addressed to my kid. My fucking envelope.
是寄给Johnny的? 你都知道些什么?
It's addressed to Johnny? What do you know about that'!
你说什么
- My envelope, it's not. - What?
这是我的信封 你他妈怎么会有我的信封?
My envelope. How the fuck did you have my envelope?
等一下 等一下! 妈的!
Wait, wait, wait! Fuck!
不!
No!
左边安全!
Clear left!
- 右边安全! - 头顶安全!
- Clear right! - Overhead check clear!
第四小队 第四小队 我们要上二楼了!
Team 4, team 4! We're moving to the second deck!
我们来搞定他们!
We'll take them!
这样 如果你愿意的话 我们来讨论一下那次事故吧
So, I'd like to discuss, if you would, the incident.
就从你们进门开始说起吧
I'd like to start from your point of entry...
你看到的 跟你经历的
what you saw and what you experienced.
你和Devin Roberts下士一起进去的
It was you and Corporal Devin Roberts.
Roberts下士 我 还有Taylor少尉
Corporal Roberts, myself, Second Lieutenant Taylor.
我们到达了一楼
We entered the first floor,
扫清了一楼的障碍 接着
cleared and neutralized the first floor, and then...
我们上了二楼
we went to the second floor.
那里有间屋子
Where there was a room.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
都他妈趴在地上!
On the fucking ground!
趴地上! 趴地上!
On the ground! On the ground!
左边安全! 见鬼
Clear left! Shit.
弟兄们 我们之间离近点! 趴地上! 趴在地上!
Boys, move in closer! Come down! Get down! Get down!
趴在地上!
On the ground! Get on the ground!
嘿 快点! 趴在地上!
Hey, hey, come on! Get on the ground.
Roberts! Roberts! 嘿 喘口气吧
Roberts! Roberts! Hey, take a breath.
趴下 趴在地上
Down. On the ground.
右边安全!
We're clear right!
趴在地上 你别惹我
On the ground. On the ground! Don't come at me.
趴地上
Get on the ground.
妈的
Shit.
嘘 给我趴好 嘿
Shh. Down. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Drummer 我们搞定了 去检查那间!
Drummer, we got this. Check that room!
收到
Roger.
Keep time.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
别碰我! 趴地上!
Get off me! Get on the ground.
- 安全吗? - 安全 Roberts
- Are we clear? - Clear, Roberts.
嘿 没事的
It's okay. Hey. Hey.
没事的 我慢慢的
It's okay. Nice and easy.
准下士 那边安全吗?
Lance Corporal, are we clean'?
- Drummer 那边安全吗? - 安全!
- Drummer, are we clear? - All clear!
屋子安全 我只是检查下尸体
Room's clear, just checking on dead.
那边那摊我还没检查
I haven't checked those motherfuckers over there yet.
- 哦 那人死透了 - 没事的
- Oh, he's good. - He's good.
上帝啊 看这些玩意
Jesus Christ. Look at this fucking shit.
呼!
Whoo!
纯平彩电...
Flat screens...
蓝钻石... 我是大熊
Blue diamond... this is big bear actual,
建筑安全 四名叛乱分子死亡
building secure, four insurgents down.
请求马上撤离 完毕
Requesting immediate evac, over.
走吧
Come on.
我操
Oh, fuck.
- 你看到没? - 我过去看看
- You see that? - I'm on it.
- Drummer - 收到
- Drummer. - Little joy.
那么...
So...
关于那次事故
About the incident.
你一直说那是一次"事故"
You keep calling it "the incident."
给你什么感受?
How does it make you feel?
它让我感觉糟透了
It makes me feel like shit.
把它写下来吧
Let's write that down.
这样可以吗?
Does that work?
抱歉 长官
I'm sorry, sir.
我感觉被背叛了
I felt betrayed.
背叛?
Betrayed?
是的 我想 如果死的是其他人 而不是他 我都不会有这种感觉
Yeah, I think if it was anybody but him, I wouldn't feel like that.
就是因为 是他
It was him.
我明白了
I see.
我还以为...我们 是在聊那个房间里的事故
I... I thought we were talking about the incident in the room.
你又说"事故"...
What you call it... What is it?
最后还是要回到"事故"
You keep going back to that incident.
那个房间...
我以为那个房间安全了
I thought the room was clear.
我以为那里安全了
The room was clear.
见鬼 妈的!
Goddamn it! Fuck!
我操!
What the fuck.
我操
Oh, fuck.
我打中了平民
I got a civilian.
呃 Dev
Oh, Dev.
Dev Dev 我...
Dev. Dev, I...
Dev!
Dev. Dev.
我操 哪儿中枪了?
Fuck. Where?
医护兵呢!
Corpsman up!
视频聊天 DevinRoberts86 密码devr86 Natalie.Drummer
Johnny很好
Johnny's great.
我他妈现在就要一个医护兵!
I need a fucking corpsman now!
真抱歉 对不起
I'm sorry. Sorry.
加油啊 Dev! 挺住 你个混蛋 挺住!
Fight, Dev! Fight, motherfucker, fight!
能跟你聊天真好
It was good to talk to you.
等不及见到你了
I can't wait to see you.
看吧
We'll see.
这里安全!
All clear!
视频聊天 Devin.sRoberts86 密码devr86 Natalie.Drummer
就是这样 长官
Yes, sir.
我以为那片区域安全了
Yeah, I thought the area was secure.
我以为安全了 但其实没有
I thought it was clear. It wasn't.
那里有一对母子
There was a mother and a son in there,
我后悔也来不及了
and I can't take that back.
没有后悔药 不能倒带 就是...
I can't rewind, you know. It's just...
那种后悔也没办法的事
just one of them things.
最近通话 Natalie - 未接听
短消息 - Devin: Gabriel是我兄弟 但是我们之间是真感情
Nat: 不 我们之间是个错误 Devin: 求你接电话 坚守信念...Devin
嘿 Johnny 我们走!
Hey, Johnny, let's go!
求你别再联系我了
嘿 宝贝 我们走吧 我是说真的!
Hey, baby, let's go! I'm serious!
Gabe
Gabe.
爸爸!
"Oh, my. Daddy!
回楼上去 好吗?
Hey, go back upstairs, okay?
妈妈要跟爸爸说点事... 现在就回去!
Mommy's gotta talk... Go back upstairs now!
嘿 亲爱的...
Hey, baby...
求你...
Please...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我感觉就像死了一样 长官 我什么都不在乎了
I just feel like I'm dead, sir. I don't give a shit anymore.
你很频繁地想到死吗?
You think about dying often?
我的天啊 你怎么总... 我不行了...
Oh, man, you just keep... You know, I can't...
抱歉 长官 我受不了了
I'm sorry, sir, I can't do this anymore.
- Gabriel - 我只想跟你谈话而已
- Gabriel. - I'm just trying to talk to you.
正确答案是什么呢 "是的"?
What is the right answer, "yes?"
那就写上 是的 这是你要的正确答案吗?
Write yes. What's the right answer?
写上正确答案 让我看看答案是什么
Write the right answer. Just give me the right answer.
你写什么我就说什么
I'll say whatever you want me to say.
你看到那些邮件 是在那件事故发生前 还是之后?
The emails. Did you know before or after the incident?
你又他妈说那是"事故"
You keep calling it the fucking incident.
你来回来去 就会说事故
You keep going back to that fucking incident.
我只是说明 又一名当时在场的战士
The fact that another Marine was present at the time
出现了令人担忧的状况
is understandably cause for concern.
你需要一个替罪羊
You need a fall guy.
就这样 你只是需要一个替罪羊
That's what this is. You just need a fall guy.
不 那是你乱七八糟的疑心病
No, that's your paranoia speaking.
我没有立场
There's no agenda here.
只是想知道发生了什么而已
I'm simply trying to understand what happened.
你不可能知道发生了什么
You can't understand what happened.
你永远都不会理解我所经历的事
You will never understand what I'm going through.
- 可能吧 - 不是可能
- Maybe. - No, not maybe.
不 我能理解负罪感 和悔恨
No, maybe I can understand guilt. I can understand regret.
我也能理解背叛
I can understand betrayal.
这些都是人类的情感困境
These are all human conditions.
接着说 你刚才提到了自杀
Now, you brought up suicide before,
这让我很担心
and that concerns me.
你想自杀吗 Gabriel?
Do you want to kill yourself, Gabriel?
你真的想自杀吗?
Do you really want to kill yourself?
是的
Yes.
那是什么让你没有动手呢?
Then what stops you?
是这个
This.
打开后备箱
Pop the trunk.
那么 接下来会怎么样呢 我带着一封
So, what happens now, I go home with this letter
上面写着我太虚弱 不能承受重压的信回到家
that says I was weak and I couldn't handle it,
然后一切就都会没事了吗?
and everything's just fine again?
不是的 我再说一次 不是
No. Again, no.
我想为你提供一些
I'd like to offer up a few suggestions
应对心理问题的建议 如果可以的话
toward dealing with those feelings, If! may.
那些不是心理问题 长官 那些是实实在在发生的事
They're not feelings, sir. They're real.
那个房间里发生的事是真的
What happened in that room is real.
我妻子的事也是实实在在的
What happened with my wife is real.
听着 你刚才所说的观点很重要
Listen, that's an important statement you just made.
这个实体的世界不是谎言 Gabriel
The physical world isn't a lie, Gabriel.
你以为那房间里安全了
You believed the room was clear.
对吧?
Yes?
对 长官
Yes, sir.
根本不值得
It's not worth it.
据说 有90%的人
They say 90% of people
从高桥上跳下来的一瞬间 都会后悔的
supposedly regret it the second they jump.
他们怎么统计出来的我也不知道
Where the fuck they got that statistic, I don't know.
可能是编的吧
Make it up.
还有 据说 那些梦魇 会无时无刻不与你如影随形
Word is, they could strike anytime, anywhere.
战争会跟着你回家
War's coming home.
没人告诉我啊
No one called me.
所以你以为我在这儿是干嘛的?
What do you think I'm doing here?
妈妈
Mom.
我不知道 你来这儿干嘛?
I don't know. What are you doing here?
Gabe!
- 听着... - 妈妈 他回来了
- Listen... - But, Mom, he's here.
你先回去 我马上去找你
I'll come get you in a second. Go on.
他们在我们的旧营地设立了情报机构
They're setting up intelligence at our old base.
这不会让你觉得心烦吗?
That doesn't trouble you?
让我觉得心烦的是 我这里有一大堆文件
What troubles me is I got a mound of paperwork
说我精神不稳定
saying I'm mentally incompetent.
这才让我心烦死了
That troubles me a fuck ton.
这些文件也把你送回家了 不是吗?
That got you home, didn't it?
我不在乎他们怎么说你
I don't care what they say about you.
世界末日要来了 狗屎都漫到耳根了
This is end-of-the-world, neck-deep-in-shit stuff.
我需要你帮忙
I need you in it.
我不干
I'm done.
- 你怎么能不干 - 我不干了 Dev
- You're never done. - I'm done, Dev.
回家后与家人的第一次相处很关键
Your first meeting back will be critical.
对Jonathan来说是的
For Jonathan.
对于你也是
And you.
我想跟你谈谈你回家后的状况
I'd like to talk about what you'll be returning to stateside.
我当然知道我家的状况
I mean, I know what I'm returning to.
是 但是万一 那里不再是你所期盼的地方了呢
Yes, but in case it isn't what you are expecting or hoping for.
我没什么期盼
I'm not hoping for anything.
那些可怕的 无法改变的事情 都是我的错
I'm responsible for these terrible things I can't change.
嘿 Gabe
Hey. Hey, Gabe.
我只是不想孩子受到伤害
I just don't want the kid to hurt.
嘿
Hey.
Gabe 你得跟孩子谈谈
Gabe, I need you to talk to him.
好
Okay.
亲爱的 真对不起
Baby, I'm so sorry.
我是说 如果你还想惩罚我的话 可以的
I mean, it's fine if you need to punish me still,
- 但是 我想要你... - 我不会惩罚你的
- but I need you to... - I'm not punishing you.
告诉我...
Tell me what...
告诉我该怎么做
Tell me what to do.
脱掉上衣
Take off your shirt.
真的吗?
Really?
好吧
Okay.
好的
你想要这样吗?
Is this what you want?
不想
No.
纹身:坚守信念
我该做些什么?
What can I do?
没什么
Nothing.
我的表到七点了 你的世界时钟呢
My watch says seven. What's your world clock say?
- 7点 - 7点
- Seven. - Seven.
我们的时间到了 长官
I guess our time is up, sir.
我没有其他地方去
I have nowhere to be.
你想继续吗?
Would you like to continue?
你我的时间都到了 感谢你花时间听我说这些
Your time is up, my time is up, but thank you for yours.
嘿 Drummer 你收到吗?
Drummer. Yo, Drummer, you copy?
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
药物会有所帮助的
The medication will be helpful.
要从这样的困境中走出 你还要做更多努力
It's gonna take a lot more than that to get you through this.
承认吧 长官 根本走不出来的
There's no getting through this, sir, admit it.
Gabe!
- 回去 快回去 - 但是 妈妈 爸爸回来了!
- Go back inside. Go back in side. - But, Mommy, he's here.
我一会儿就去叫你
I'll come get you in a second. Go on.
你干嘛这么在乎我?
Why do they give a shit about me?
他们都不在乎我 我也不在乎他们
They don't give a shit about me, I don't give a shit about them.
Gabe
Gabe.
我们能做到的
We can make this work.
求你了
Come on, please.
Nat!
我的儿子呢?
Where's my kid?
你不冷静下来的话 我没法跟你说话
I'm not gonna talk to you if you don't calm down.
你没法什么?
You're not gonna what?
你不冷静下来的话 我没法跟你说话
I'm not gonna talk to you if you don't calm down.
我冷静得很 现在就把儿子给我送出来
I'm calm. Get my kid out here now.
- Gabe 你能不能小声点 - Nat 我要我儿子
- Gabe, keep your voice down, please. - Nat, I wanna see my kid.
我知道学校里的人 在对孩子们做什么可怕的事
I know what they're doing with the kids in school.
我要我儿子 我现在就想见我儿子
I wanna see my child. I want to see my kid now!
我报警了 因为你吓到孩子了
I'm on the phone with the police 'cause you're scaring our kid.
- Johnny! - 别喊了 他妈的冷静点
- Johnny! - Stop. Calm the fuck down.
- 我要我儿子... - Gabe 别他妈发疯了!
- I wanna see my... - Gabe, fucking stop! Stop!
我要见我儿子!
I want to see my kid!
我是美国海军陆战队员 我要见我儿子!
I'm a United States Marine. I want to see my son!
我知道学校里都对孩子做些什么
I know what's happening to kids inside the school.
我就他妈想见我儿子! Jon有麻烦了
I want to see my fucking child! Jon is in trouble.
Gabe 别闹了!
Gabe, stop! Stop!
- 别闹了 Gabe! - 你看见什么了 Drummer?
- Stop, Gabe! - What'd you see, Drummer'?
请派警察过来 我丈夫有枪
I need the police. My husbands got a gun
他去了我儿子的学校
and he's going to my kid's school.
- 在哪儿? - 我该怎么办?
- What's over there? - What do I do?
- 你是谁? - 回答问题.
- Who are you? - Answer the question.
Gunshot
- 你是说? - Charles 我叫Charles
- Who are you? - Charles, my name's Charles.
呼哈
Hoorah.
你从哪儿搞到这个信封?
How did you get this envelope?
这个信封上写的是我儿子的地址 这是我的信封 你怎么得到的?
It's an envelope addressed to my kid. My fucking envelope.
- 我不懂你在说什么! - 你怎么得到的?
- I don't know what you're talking about! - How did you get this?
那些不是心理问题 长官 那些是实实在在发生的事
They're not feelings, sir. They're real.
那个房间里发生的事是真的
What happened in that room is real.
我妻子的事也是实实在在的
What happened with my wife is real.
Gabriel
Devin 我在后门这边 我要进去了
Devin, I'm at the back entrance. I'm going in.
嘿 小伙子 是爸爸 你没事吧?
Hey, pal. Hey, it's Pop. You okay?
爸爸
- Daddy. - Yeah.
我要你别出声
I need you to be quiet.
我们现在一起离开这地方 好吗?
We're gonna get out of this place now, all right?
- 好吗? 你相信我吗? - 相信
- Okay? You trust me? - Yeah. Yeah.
我相信你 你是个大男孩了
I trust you. Come on, be a big boy now.
走吧 走
Here we go. Up.
爸爸 爸爸
Daddy. Daddy.
等等
Hold on.
Dev 请回答 出来吧
Dev, made contact. Coming out.
- Johnny! - 小心 小心 后退
- Johnny! - Back, back, back, back.
好了 没事了 接着走
All right, you're okay. Come on.
Johnny!
- 小心脚下 - Gabe!
- Watch your footing. - Gabe!
房里有人开枪 他带走了我的孩子 我该怎么办?
Shooting in the house. He's got my son. He's got my son. What do I do?
警察!
Police!
有人开枪!
Shots fired!
回去!
Go back in!
你会没事的 你会没事的 来 过来
You're okay. Okay. You're okay. Come on, we'll go over here.
我出去一下 你就在这儿别动
I'm going to go. Stay right there.
- 你没事吧? - 没事
- You okay, buddy? - Yeah.
无论发生什么 你都会好好的 明白吗?
Whatever happens, you'll be fine, you understand?
Dev 快进来 Dev Dev!
Dev, come in, Dev. Dev!
怎么回事
The fucking thing, man.
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
我害怕
I'm scared.
不 你不能害怕
Hey, no, you're not.
Huh?
- 好吗? - 好
Okay? - Yeah.
没事的
It's all right.
别哭了 你会没事的 好吧?
Don't cry. You're gonna be fine. Okay?
好
Yeah.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Johnny 你会没事的
Johnny, you'll be fine.
Yeah.
我给你准备了个东西 还记得吗?
I got something for you, too. Here. Remember that'?
- 这是谁? - 是我和妈妈
- Who's that? - It's me and Mom.
这是你的妈妈
She's your mom.
她是我的一切
She's my everything.
她是你的妈妈
She's your mom.
是我的一切
That's my everything.
Yeah.
是我的一切
That's my everything.
Jon 你会没事的
Jon, you'll be fine.
坚强点 有我陪着你 儿子
Be strong. I got you, son.
警察! 出来!
Police! Come out!
Go! Go! Go!
那是啥?
What's that?
小熊糖
Gummy bears.
你最喜欢的糖 是吧? 你最喜欢的
Your favorite candy, right? That's your favorite candy.
是的
Yeah.
我还记得
I remember.
那是你最喜欢的糖吧?
Is that your favorite candy, huh?
- 是的 - 红色的 是吧?
- Yeah. - The red ones, right?
Johnny的最爱
Johnny's favorite candy.
- Hmm? - Yeah.
你把红色的都吃了
You eat them red ones.
我很快就回来
I'll be back in five seconds, okay?
说 "好的 爸爸 我明白"
Say, "Yeah, Dad, I understand."
好的 爸爸 我明白
Yeah, Dad, I understand.
- 警察! 别动! - 爸爸!
- Police, don't move! - Daddy!
爸爸!
Daddy!
Johnny 别看!
Johnny, don't look!
Gabriel!
你怎么知道我的名字? 你怎么知道我的名字?
How do you know my name? How do you know my name?
Drummer 我们搞定了 去检查那间屋子!
Drummer, we got this. Check the last room.
你没事吧?
Okay. You okay?
没事
- Yeah. Yeah. - Huh'?
Devin 第二小队呼叫 Dev
Devin, team two here, Dev.
Dev 你收到吗? Dev!
Dev, are you tracking me? Dev!
我他妈有大麻烦了 收到吗?
I'm in deep shit here. Do you copy?
Dev 你收...妈的
Dev, do you... Fuck.
我们没事的 没事的
We're okay. We're okay.
Yeah.
我连个医生的电话都没有
I don't even have the doctor's number.
- 你是谁? - 他在这里 他在这里
- Who are you? - He's here. He's here.
你是谁?
Who are you? Who are you?
待在那儿别动 Jon
Stay right there, Jon.
- 你是谁? - 是我
- Who are you? - It's me.
你到底是谁?
Who are you?
你在跟谁打电话?
Who are you talking to?
是我
It's me.
妈妈
Mom.
嘘 我知道你在对孩子做什么
Shh. I know what you're doing to the kids.
我的孩子应该和他妈妈在一起 他妈妈呢?
My kid was with his mother. Where is she?
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
是我
It's me.
你不是...
You aren't...
Gabe
Gabe.
她在哪儿? 我孩子的妈妈在哪儿?
Where is she? Where's my kid's mother?
她在哪儿? 坐下
Where is she? Where is she? Down.
坐地上 坐下
Get down, get down.
我老婆在哪儿? 我老婆 Natalie Drummer
Where's my wife? Natalie Drummer is my wife.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
Gabriel
- 她在哪儿? - 不要 Gabriel...
- Where is she? - No, Gabriel...
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
- 她在哪儿? - 我就在这儿
- Where is she? - I'm right here.
- Natalie Drummer在哪儿? - Gabriel 求你了
- Natalie Drummer, where is she? - Gabriel, please.
她在哪儿?
Where is she? Where is she?
他妈的我老婆在哪儿?
Where is my fucking wife?
不要 不要
Don't. No, no, no.
不要
Don't.
[voices shouting, gunfire
那些不是心理问题 长官 那些是实实在在发生的事
They're not feelings, sir. They're real.
那个房间里发生的事是真的
What happened in that room is real.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
天啊...
Oh' my...
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起
没关系 爸爸
It's okay, Dad.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean it.
我不知道...
I didn't know.
我很困惑 我没搞清
I was confused. I was confused.
我不知道
I didn't know. I didn't know.
Natty 对不起
Natty, I'm sorry.
我糊涂了 我不知道...
I was confused. I didn't...
♪ In this heart ♪
♪ Lies for you ♪
♪ A lark born ♪
♪ Only for you ♪
♪ Who sings only ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ My love, my love ♪
♪ My love ♪
你知道吗 我在想....
You know, I was thinking about...
在想...
I was thinking about...
过去 我们都是寄信的
You know, in the old days, we used to send letters.
这些是我写给你的
I wrote these for you.
那可是超级庞大的一个工程
It was, like, a big process.
根本是不可能任务
It was, like, impossible.
信必须是手写的
You had to, like, write it by hand.
♪ My love, my love ♪
现在有了电子邮件 视频聊天...
Now we got email and Skype...
就好像我就在你身边 明白吗?
It's almost like I'm here already, you know?
♪ ...is my grief for you ♪
不!
No!
♪ For only ♪
♪ The loss of you ♪
我不是妈妈 但是我肯定
I ain't Mom, but I damn sure am gonna tell my kid
我也想在你下车时跟你说"我爱你" 是吧?
I love him when he gets out the car, as'! right?
是
Yeah.
所以我们想个能过得去的办法吧
So we gotta come up some kind of little middle ground,
比如一个暗号什么的
like a secret word or something.
♪ My love, my love ♪
"友军倒下"好不好?
What about "man down"?
"友军倒下"? - 挺好的吧
Man clown? - That's pretty good.
- 我很喜欢 - 我也喜欢
Yeah, I like that. - / like it, too.
听起来多男人啊
Damn sure is manly enough.
没其他人会知道这是什么意思
Nobody will know what we're talking about when we say it.
所以 如果我想说"我爱你"的话 我会怎么说?
So, anytime I want to say I love you what am I going to say to you?
- "友军倒下" - 很好
- Man down. - All right, good.
好啦 下车吧
All right, get out the car.
♪ All loneliness have died ♪
"友军倒下"
♪ My love, my love ♪
不! Johnny 不!
No! Johnny, no!
♪ My love ♪
♪ I will have you ♪
嘿 "友军倒下"
Hey, man down.
"友军倒下"
Man down.
去吧 小牛仔
Little cowboy, go ahead.
♪ In my arms ♪
祝你一天过得愉快
Have a good day, bud.
你也是
You too.
我爱你
I love you.
真的?
How much?
♪ My love ♪
每五个伊拉克/阿富汗老兵中就有一个有战后应激创伤 20万老兵每晚都无家可归
每天都有20名老兵自杀